One of the companions was
reported to
him.
The wife reported to the
brother who
came to visit him.
In Medina.
And that one went to report
to
the Prophet Sallallahu Alaihi
Wasallam.
This companion, that was
Abdullah Ibn Amr
al-As.
He did notice to sleep in the
night.
And he would fast every day.
So his wife was feeling.
He would not come near the
wife.
The Prophet didn't like it
Sallallahu Alaihi
Wasallam.
Something similar to that was
reported about
Abul Zerrin al-Ghifari also.
So Ekhwa.
Those who go beyond limits.
Ghalin Fidin.
We just explained Gulu Fidin.
For example fasting
throughout the day time.
Never breaking fast.
Or never observing sleep.
Not sleeping.
Wa inna li jasadika alayka
haqqan.
And your body has a right
over
you.
So sleep sometimes.
Wake up sometimes.
Some people abandon their
wives.
Some women abandon their
husbands.
And making kiamu led.
And fasting.
So that's why the husband
cannot come
near her.
That's why she can't cook for
her
husband.
This Gulu.
So the Prophet said alayhi
salatu wassalam.
So in Fadim, in Ummati ila
tana
luhu ma shafa'ati.
Two groups of people in my
ummah.
My special Shafa'a.
Mentioned for special people
in special situations
will not reach them.
The first one.